Alexandru George Grumeza

Str.Costache Negruzii No 1, Constanta, 900258 (RO) +40(737)629075

Alexgrumeza7@icloud.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Dedicated waiter committed to providing helpful, fast, and accurate service to managers. Demonstrate active listening and communication skills to ensure managers are satisfied and happy. Experience in various settings, including family restaurants, bars, cafeterias. Comfortable serving patrons of various age ranges and backgrounds. Determined team player striving to deliver the highest quality service alongside food service staff.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

waiter, Fratelli Restaurant. Constanta, Constanta

Jun. 2019 – Present

- -Providing excellent wait service to ensure satisfaction
- -Taking customer orders and delivering food and beverages
- -Making menu recommendations, answering questions and sharing additional information with restaurant manager
- -Ability to perform well in fast-paced environments

waiter, Curtea Berarilor Restaurant. Constanta, Constanta

Jun. 2017 – Sep. 2017

- -Providing excellent wait service to ensure satisfaction
- -Taking customer orders and delivering food and beverages
- -Making menu recommendations, answering questions and sharing additional information with restaurant manager
- -Ability to perform well in fast-paced environments

waiter, Caffe Del Mar Club. Constanta-Mamaia, Constanta

Jun. 2016 – Sep. 2016

- -Providing excellent wait service to ensure satisfaction
- -Taking customer orders and delivering food and beverages

- -Making menu recommendations, answering questions and sharing additional information with restaurant manager
- -Ability to perform well in fast-paced environments

assistent waiter, Budha Bar Restaurant. Constanta, Constanta

- Participates in rotational service delivery schedule, working in casual dining service and various other food and beverage service venues. Observes all established security and guest privacy procedures when delivering to staterooms.
- Provides assistance and support to assigned team of Waiters while working in the dining room to ensure efficient and seamless service delivery of all meals to guests.
- Learns and uses appropriate food and wine terminology and pronunciation to enhance the guest's dining experience. Becomes familiar with menu descriptions and wine lists in order to discuss items appropriately with guests.
- Presents both food and beverage menus to guests, suggests dinner courses, appropriate wines and answers questions regarding menu and wine selections per Gold Anchor Standards. Makes recommendations to entice guests while meeting management goals to reduce particular inventory stock.
- Relays order to galley as required and serves courses from galley and beverages from various locations.

EDUCATION

Anghel Saligny, Bucharest, Bucharest

highschool, Jun. 2019

SKILLS

teamwork, persistence

verbal communication

able to work as part of a team

friendly, polite and helpful

good memory

friendly, polite and helpful.

excellent communication skills